# **JAMES ROGERS**

UI / Graphic Design

Web Development

Front-End Development Product Design

jamesrogers.io – napacreativeco.com 707.365.3802

hello@napacreativeco.com

#### **About Me**

I'm a 32 year old Front End Developer and Graphic Designer based in Napa, California. I focus my time on creating Websites and Graphics for friends, bands, brands, and small businesses. On my free time I like to produce music, read and hanging out with my family.

#### Skills

Photoshop Figma HTML

Illustrator WordPress CSS / SCSS

AfterEffects React JavaScript / jQuery

Premiere Gatsby PHP

## **Experience**

Lead Developer, Designer

Napa Creative Company

Napa, California 03.2020 – Present Projects range from Merchandise design, Web Design, Web Development, Logo Design, Packaging Design, Menu design, Product Photography, and more.

## Sr. Graphic Designer

Gaby Inc.

Sebastopol, California 01.2019 – 03.2020 I was responsible for Designing and Developing new Websites for a collection of companies within our 'House of Brands'. Other projects include Packaging design, Trade show design, Menu design and many

### **Lead Designer**

Sonoma Pacific Dist.

Santa Rosa, California 11.2016 – 12.2018 My responsibilities ranged from Web Design and Development, in-house and as a service to our brands, Packaging design, Trade show

design, Compliance review, and more.

#### **Education**

Code Academy Completed courses on JavaScript, Ruby,

more.

PHP, Python and SQL.

Udemy Completed multiple courses on JavaScript &

ES6, React with and without Redux, Front-End Web Development, Full Stack

Development, Swift and more.

**Skillshare** Completed courses on Graphic Design

fundamentals, Typography, AfterEffects, Photo Editing and Facebook Advertising.

**High school Diploma** Forest Charter School, Class of 2007,

Truckee, California